<tips> 
	<tip> 
		<title>Nutrition</title> 
		<body><![CDATA[<ul><li>Add canned tomatoes to your favorite dips and pastas for an extra boost of lycopene, an antioxidant naturally found in tomatoes that helps fight disease. Thanks to the canning process, canned tomatoes are actually a better source of lycopene than their fresh counterpart. 
<br><li>Add canned pumpkin to your favorite puddings or pancake batter. It is an excellent source of vitamin A, containing more than three times the Daily Value compared to an equal amount of fresh, cooked pumpkin. Don’t have canned pumpkin? Try canned, puréed sweet potatoes!
<br></ul>]]></body>
	</tip> 
	
	<tip> 
		<title>Convenience</title> 
		<body><![CDATA[<ul><li>Use canned beans in your favorite recipes instead of soaking and cooking down fresh or dried. Canned food is already cooked in the can and comes in many varieties, saving you precious prep time.
<br><li>Prepare a quick potato salad with a can of potatoes. No peeling, boiling or chopping adds up to big time savings.
<br></ul>]]></body> 
	</tip> 
	
	<tip> 
		<title>Taste</title> 
		<body><![CDATA[<ul><li>Spice up a traditional bean dip with canned tomatoes with diced chilies, sharp Cheddar cheese and a can of corn. Serve with tortilla chips on the side to balance out the zing! 
<br><li>Top off a great meal with a refreshing homemade sorbet. Freeze your favorite canned fruit in heavy syrup until firm and then purée in a food processor. Serve immediately for a deliciously simple and nutritious dessert.
<br></ul>]]></body> 
	</tip> 
	
	<tip> 
		<title>Value</title> 
		<body><![CDATA[<ul><li>Make restaurant quality greens and beans at home by sautéing poached escarole with cannellini beans, garlic, and bacon and/or prosciutto. Who says gourmet dining has to be at an expensive restaurant? 
<br><li>Fresh fruits and veggies spoiling faster than you can eat them? Stock up on your favorite canned fruits and veggies to enjoy on your own time. Since canned foods are shelf-stable, you can buy them in bulk to keep on hand, which saves you money and time going to the store. By the time food is consumed, fresh, frozen and canned fruits and vegetables may be nutritionally similar. 
<br></ul>]]></body> 
	</tip>	
</tips>	
 